branded3.com 2017-04-19

# Privacy Policy | Branded3

### Introduction

Branded3 Search Limited is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy outlines the basis on which any personal information we collect from you, or that you provide us with, will be processed by us.

This privacy policy only relates to personal data collected by us via our website(s), emails or telephone calls. You should be aware that if you access third party websites, using links provided on our website(s), these websites are outside our control and have their own privacy policies governing the use of personal data and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.

### Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website(s). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use any of our online services, subscribing to our newsletter or requesting any of our goods or services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our website(s).

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

Details of transactions you carry out through our website(s) and of the fulfilment of your orders may also be collected by us.

### IP addresses

When you visit our website(s), we may collect information about your computer, including your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet), operating system and browser type, for system and website administration and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns and does not identify any individual.

### Website traffic monitoring

We may also obtain and compile or appoint third parties to obtain and compile on our behalf, details of your visits to our website(s) including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, the resources that you access, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing, marketing purposes or otherwise. This data does not identify any individual but may identify organisations and we may use that information in managing our relationship with those organisations, for example, in considering how to develop the services that we offer them.

### Cookies

Our website(s) use cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website(s) in order to help us provide you with a good experience when you browse and use our website(s) and to enable us to improve our website(s). For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them, see our Cookies Policy detailed below.

### Use made of personal information

We may use personal information held about you in order to:

Ensure that content from our website(s) is presented in the most effective manner.

Identify you each time you visit our website(s).

Improve our website(s) and services.

Process requests, orders or applications submitted by you.

Carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

Notify you about changes to our goods and/or services.

Carry out demographics of users of our website(s).

Provide, or permit our Affiliates and/or selected third parties to use your data to provide you with information about goods and services, which may be of interest to you.  
Personal information provided to us via our website(s), emails and telephone calls will be used for the purposes explained at the time of collection in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act).

### Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. At each point of data collection or registration you are given the opportunity to tell us that you do not wish us to use your personal data to contact you about goods and services which might be of interest to you, by ticking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your personal data.

We may wish to share personal information with our Affiliates and selected third parties so they may contact you about goods and services which may be of interest to you. You can exercise your right to prevent us from disclosing your personal data to such third parties for this purpose by ticking the relevant box on the forms being used to collect your data.

If at any time you want to alter your marketing communication preferences or for us to stop sending marketing communications to you, please contact our Database Manager at the address specified at the end of this privacy policy.

### Consent

By providing personal data to us you are consenting to the processing of such data by us as described in this privacy policy.

### Where we store your personal data

The personal data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Security

We hold your personal data in accordance with the security provisions of the Act.

### Access to information

The Act gives you the right to ask us, in writing, for a copy of the personal data held about you (“subject access request”) and to request that we correct any inaccuracies in that information. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

### Verifying, updating and amending your personal information

If, at any time, you want to verify, update or amend your personal data you may email us using the link below. Alternatively, you may write to the Database Manager at the address provided at the end of this privacy policy. Verification, updating or amendment of personal data takes place within two working days of receipt of the request if made online and 10 working days if made offline.

### Notification of changes to our privacy policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post such changes on this page.

### Contact

Any questions, comments or requests regarding this privacy policy or the processing of your personal data are welcomed and should be addressed to:

Database Manager  
Branded3 Search Limited  
2nd floor, 2180 Century Way  
Thorpe Park  
Leeds  
LS15 8ZB

### Cookie policy

### Introduction

When we provide services, we want to make them easy, useful and reliable. Where services are delivered on the internet, this sometimes involves placing small amounts of information on your device, for example, a computer or mobile phone, if you agree. These small files of information are known as cookies. Cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website(s), which helps us to provide you with a better experience when browsing our website(s) and also allows us to improve our website(s). Cookies cannot be used to identify you personally.

Examples of how cookies are used to improve services for you are:

Enabling a service to recognise your device so you don’t have to give the same information several times during one task.

Recognising that you may already have given a username and password so you don’t need to do it for every web page requested.

Measuring how many people are using services, so they can be made easier to use and there’s enough capacity to ensure they are fast.  
Our cookies aren’t used to identify you personally. They’re just here to make the website(s) work better for you. In fact, you can manage and/or delete these small files as you wish.

To learn more about cookies and how to manage them, [click here](http://aboutcookies.org/).

### The cookies we use and how we use them

Cookies for managing your current visit:

 **Name                          Typical content                        Expires**  
Site session             Randomly generated text       When user exits browser

### Cookies for improving service

We use several different types of cookie on our website(s); these are:

 **Session cookies:** These are temporary cookies, which are stored on your device for as long as you’re browsing our website(s), and remember such things as adding a product to a shopping basket.

 **Persistent cookies** : This type of cookie stays on your device even once you’ve closed your browser, and typically remains for around 30 days. They help websites to personalise your experience by remembering certain products you’ve viewed or bought before.

 **Third-party cookies:** This type of cookie will collect information which is sent back to a website other than the one you’re currently browsing, and is used to improve user experience on our website(s).

The data collected is completely anonymous and can be used, for example, by advertisers to find out where and when users are clicking on their ads.
